行了 别浪费时间了 这又不算啥
Sure,let's give up now.It's no big deal.
不过是Phapmacide 巡回演唱会的首场罢了
It's just pharmacide.Just their tour kickoff.
依我看 即使错过了史上最疯魔的派对 也没什么了不起?
I mean,who cares if we miss the most insane party in the world?
跟我来吧 phoeb.
Come on,phoeb.
孤注一掷
Victory or death.
说不定还有蛋糕作奖励
Or possibly cake.
小心点 真对不起咯
Look,I'm sorry.
不好意思 你要的咖啡就到了
Sorry,your caffeine fix is on its way.
先别挂机好吗?
Will you hold on?
我们是DJ的助理
We're the dj's assistants.
你不能过去
Hold on.
抱歉 我俩都是他的助理
No,I said we both work for him.
你说她吧?
You mean her.
DJ是女的
The dj's a  she-jay.
没啥 Dave.
It's okay,dave.
她是我的特别助理
She's my "plus one.
那个也算是吧
" make that "plus two.
" 难道你一点也不害怕吗?
" you weren't worried,were you?
如果不全盘托出 小心会遭受惩罚哦
Yes.And there will be punishment unless you tell us everything.
你真的在那里呆了一晚?
You've been here all night?
后来我们跟着乐队去了总统套房
After the party,we went up to the presidential suite with the band.
真是忒大 共10个房间啊
It was ginormous.Like,ten rooms.
喝酒 抽大麻之余 我们还在巨型等离子电视上玩"鼓神鼓"
We had a few drinks and some weed and played "drummer god" on this giant plasma tv.
她超抢眼哦
Which she rocked,by the way.
我真是恨死你了
I think I hate you right now.
Colt领我上了天台 游泳池的入口被锁了
Colt took me up to the roof,but by then the gate to the pool was locked.
所以那里空无一人
So no one was up there.
我们偷偷翻了进泳池,然后裸泳
So we just climbed over and jumped down and,um... went skinny dipping.
你们亲热了吗?
Did you do it?
没有 他很体贴
No. He was so sweet.
后来他弹起了吉他 还写了首歌给我
Later,he played his guitar,and he wrote a song for me.
天啊!
Oh,my god!
Jord 你的脚怎么了?
Jord,what happened to your foot?
可能是你落地时扭到脚了
Maybe you twisted your ankle when you jumped.
也可能是过敏
Or it could be your allergies.
我阿姨对感冒药过敏 她的手都会像棉花糖人一样肿
My aunt was allergic to some cold medication,and her hands swelled up like the marshmallow man's.
Jord 没事吧?
Jord,are you okay?
Jordan!
Foreman竟然要我在这分辨率超低的 微型屏幕上读片
Foreman expects me to read an x-ray on this itty-bitty screen.
他该顺便给我邮个大点的电话
He should have emailed me a larger phone.
你干嘛收拾行李啊?
Why are you packing?
今天下午我们要去 参加药理学暨和公共管理会议
We're leaving this afternoon for the conference on pharmacology and public policy.
- 我们? - 我和你提过的
- We? - We discussed this.
数周前就写在你的日历上了
It's been on your calendar for weeks.
- 斋月也记在日历上啊 - 你就把这个当成放假吧
- So has ramadan. - Think of it as a vacation.
我不管阿第伦达克山的空气
Nice,healthy adirondack air.
是否清新怡人 你来就是了
Or not. I don't care.You're coming with.
你才应该跟我走呢
You should come with me.
全国枕头大战争霸赛
State pillow fighting championships.
廉价啤酒 湿身T恤 应有尽有
Dollar beers,wet t-shirts.
用Eddie Money的话来说 (摇滚歌手) 我得到了两张去天堂的入门券 (歌曲名)
In the words of the philosopher eddie money,I've got two tickets to paradise.
House 你搬进来时我答应你的医生 我会陪着你
House,when you moved in I promised your therapist  I'd be here for you.
如果我去开会 就不能看着你了
I can't be here if I'm there.
除非你与我同行 所以这是毋庸置疑的
Unless you're there too.So it's not a discussion.
行吧
Fine.
我会告诉Foreman 那个严重水肿的16岁患者要等等了
I'll let foreman know that the 16-year-old patient  with severe edema can wait.
别急 对她的病我还是没啥头绪
Relax.I've got no idea what's wrong with her.
也有可能 她根本死不了
So odds are,not fatal.
我不去 我不去!
Still not going!
这是横纹肌溶解症
She's got rhabdo.
谁想去枕头大战争霸赛啊?
Who wants to come to the pillow fighting championships?
Rutgers 今年阵容强大哦.
Rutgers has got a great team this year.
他们的主力没有转成职业选手真是太好了
I'm so glad their anchor didn't turn pro.
16岁少女的关节突然像80岁老妇
A 16-year-old girl suddenly has the joints of an 80-year-old.
我们能稍微谈谈这个吗?
You think we can discuss this for a second?
毫无疑问就是横纹肌溶解症 她晕倒后病情恶化
It's rhabdo.The patient gave you the answer.She fell down and went boom.
再过1小时就得去看比赛 不如来玩猜大小决定谁去?
We have to leave in an hour,so should we eenie-meenie?
摔倒仅能解释小腿病变 解释不了手部肿胀
The fall would explain the lower leg damage,but not the swollen hands.
着地引起肌肉损伤
Hard landing caused crushed muscles.
肌肉损伤释放毒素入血 进而导致手脚肿胀
Crushed muscles released toxins into the blood stream.Toxins caused swelling in the hands and legs.
归根结底还是横纹肌溶解症 还剩59分钟
Just another way of saying it's rhabdo.59 minutes.
她少人照看 父母都是建筑师
She's a credit card kid.Her parents are architects.
现在都在上海赶项目
They're working on a project in shanghai.
你能在一间屋子里 坐得离Chase更远些么?
Could you be sitting any further away from chase  and still be in the same room?
不一定是横纹肌溶解症 深部静脉血栓也会导致肿胀
It doesn't have to be rhabdo.The swelling could also be caused by deep vein thrombosis.
她也有过敏 可能是过敏反应 或者有心脏问题被我们忽略了--
She has allergies.Could be anaphylaxis or some heart condition that we don't--
除了横纹肌溶解症 其他都不可能
it can't really be any of those things since it's rhabdo.
我肯定这是横纹肌溶解症 Foreman也知道
I know it's rhabdo.Foreman knows it's rhabdo.
即使chanse嘴里不说 心里也知道的
Deep in his heart,even chase knows it's rhabdo.
人人都知晓 只有你被瞒在鼓里 很不爽吧?
Isn't it annoying when everybody in the room knows  something you don't?
我去做检查
I'll test for everything.
他是混蛋
He's an ass.
增强显影准备好了
Contrast is ready.
她早就怀疑我有外遇了
She already thinks I'm cheating on her.
可能House希望藉此 让你亲口告诉她
Maybe this is house's way of telling you to talk to her.
行啊 亲爱的 今天过得咋样啊? 忘记说 我杀了人
Sure. How was your day,honey?By the way,I killed someone.
如果我说了 她就会一辈子背着这个包袱
If I tell her,that's dumping a burden on her forever.
成
Okay.
没有发现栓塞或血栓
No sign of obstructions or clots.
house 直说吧 你来干啥
Tell me what you came here for,house.
我有正当的理由
I've got a legitimate medical reason.
那你肯定很自豪咯
You must be so proud.
我刚刚失忆了
I've forgotten it.
那也不算啥 我只是找籍口来看看Patty和Selma姐妹
I guess it's no big deal,since I was only using it as an excuse to come check out patty and selma.
我好惭愧 我都没有给你的老二起名字呢
I feel bad.I haven't named your testicles.
大伙都说你找到了个人最惹火低胸装
Word on the street is you set a new personal best for low-cut.
我不懂你为啥 给她们起个阿姨的名字
I don't know why you chose to give them the names of somebody's aunts.
赞美之词而已 她们太惹火了
It's a compliment.They're always smokin'.
想起了
Oh,I remember.
我要你批准一个未成年患者出院
I need you to authorize the medical discharge of a minor.
就是我手里这一份
That's why I'm holding this in my hand.
我还没有做完检查 但是--- 你的发信箱是正常的3倍大
I haven't finished testing yet,but it's rh-- your outbox is three times normal size.
我没有其他意思的
It's not a metaphor.
这周我还有一堆活要干
There's a lot to be done before the weekend.
你可以把文件拿回家
You could take the papers home with you.
除非你不准备回家
Unless you're not gonna be home.
除非你准备去参加某个医学会议
Unless you were,for example,going to a medical conference.
- 我和wilson一起去 - 我也是
- I'm driving up with wilson. - Me too.
- 你没有登记参加啊 - 你真关注我啊
- *** - I love that you checked.
- 可wilson说-- 我收了个病人吗?没错
- But wilson said-- that I have a case?Yeah.
你签的就是她的出院批准书
You're authorizing the discharge right now.
刚刚那个确实是比喻哦 (发信箱=翘臀)
That  was  a metaphor.
我没空
Busy right now.
- 他不行了吗? - 嗯
- Is he dying? - Yeah.
再有十分钟就不行了?
In the next ten minutes?
可惜不是 他很遭罪
Unfortunately,no.He's in a lot of pain.
我琢磨过了 你没错 我应该去参加大会
I've thought about it.You're right.I should go to the conference.
因为你发现Cuddy也去
You found out cuddy's going.
老天啊
Oh,god,no.
她真是破坏王
She'll ruin everything.
我们2小时后启程
We leave in two hours.
请给我用些吗啡
Please...morphine.
我会一直陪着你的 Joseph.
I'm right here.I'm right here,joseph.
我要离开2天
Two days away.
我要不要带球球去呢? 你不能走 你点着了火
You think I should pack ball-y?You can't leave.You lit a fuse.
就该留下来看起爆
You need to watch the bomb go off.
如果你保持缄默 炸弹也会自动引爆
The bomb was gonna go off on its own if you kept quiet.
要不就编个够说服力的谎 不然就告诉她实情
So now you either have to come up with a convincing lie,or tell her the truth.
自己选吧
Your choice.
- 肌酸激酶提示横纹肌溶解症 - 当然啦
- Ck levels point to rhabdo. - Of course.
但影像学检查没有提示肌肉损伤
Except for the part where imaging shows no sign of muscle crush.
我是你的主治医师
I'm your doctor.
lars ulrich 史上最著名的重金属摇滚鼓手 听过这曲子吗?
This is lars ulrich,the greatest metal drummer of all-time.You know the song?
来 这是你的鼓槌
Good. Drumstick.
另外一个
Another drumstick.
我想你像那晚一样跟着节奏敲鼓
I want you to rock out to the music the way you did last night.
来吧 这可是经典医学检查哦 希波克拉底也用过 开始啦
Go on.This is a classic medical test.Hippocrates used it.Let's go.
来吧 跟住节奏! 敲高踏钹时要双手交叉
Come on,you've gotta keep time!Cross over on the high hat.
来激烈的!
Let's head bang!
House 你在干吗?
House,what are you doing?
检查提示低钾
The chart said her potassium's low.
横纹肌溶解症会升高血钾 拨浪鼓也会哦
Rhabdo elevates the potassium.And monkey drums.
Ergo... 那昨晚你的血钾一定低得可怕咯
Ergo...   the levels must've been really low  last night.
- 那就会导致... - 我的手动不了
- Which causes... - I can't move them.
暂时性肌肉瘫痪
Temporary muscle paralysis.
根据肌肉瘫痪的状况 她绝对不可能又爬楼梯 又翻墙到游泳池
Given this rate of muscle fatigue,there's no way she could've climbed stairs and then a fence to the pool.
低钾意味着没有翻墙 即没有外伤史
Low potassium means no jump,means no trauma.
检查证实了横纹肌溶解症
Tests mean "yes rhabdo.
就是说 某个因素同时引起了 横纹肌溶解症和低钾
"  ergo,something else caused both the rhabdo and the low potassium.
这次从详细查问病史入手
This time start by getting an accurate history.
当心了 我们的病人是个大话精
Be careful.Our patient's a big fat liar.
你昨晚到底干了什么?
What did you really do last night?
我们得找出低钾的原因
We need to find the cause of your low potassium.
你可能患有肾功能异常 白血病或腺瘤
You could have a kidney disorder,leukemia,adenoma.
我们要知道你磕了什么药 喝了什么酒
We need to know about any drugs or alcohol.
任何对你健康造成损害的因素
Anything that might have threatened your health.
说吧 Jord
Come on,jord.
好吧 我们没和乐队一起过夜
Okay,we didn't spend the night with the band.
不要告诉我其他朋友
You can't tell our friends.
你听说过"短剑风云之女王战士"吗?
Have you heard of stiletto: warrior queen of space?
是部漫画对吧?
It's a comic book right?
- 谢谢 - 没错
- Thank you. - Yeah.
这是部超正的科幻电视剧
Yes,and a freaking amazing new sci-fi series.
他们要把它拍成动作片
And they're filming the motion picture now.
这是一部前传
It's a prequel.
其她女生是不会明白的
The other girls wouldn't get it.
只有Phoebe理解我的痴迷
Only phoebe understands my passion.
只有Phoebe理解武士道精神
Only phoebe understands the bushido of the heel.
那昨晚到底发生了什么事?
So what actually happened last night?
我们和其他朋友想进入 Adams酒店的Pharmacide巡回 派对
We were with our friends trying to get into the pharmacide tour party at the adams.
这时我发现 Jeffrey Keener也在那儿
And then I found out that jeffrey keener's gonna be there.
我在跟他的微博
I follow his tweets.
真可悲 还得向你们解释
It's tragic that I have to explain this.
他是短剑风云第一部的作者
He's the creator of stiletto issue number one.
- 电视剧的创作人 - 神一样的人物
- And the tv show. - He's a god.
于是你们冲上前去?
So did you guys go up to him?
上帝 不 我们是有原则的
God,no.We keep a ten-foot rule.
我们绝不会冒昧上前去打扰别人
It's not stalking if you don't go up to the person and bother them.
- 所以我们跟着他到处转 - 小心翼翼地
- So we just followed him around. - Discreetly.
他半小时后便离开了 去酒店楼下餐厅吃饭
He ditched after half an hour and went down to the hotel restaurant for a late dinner.
- 你们也跟着去了? - 小心翼翼地
- And you went with him? - Discreetly.
这实在太酷了
We played it so cool.
两小时里 我们像他一样生活
For two hours,we lived his life.
我们模仿他做的一切 吃着和他一样的晚餐
We did everything he did.Ate the exact same meal he ate.
真酷
Cool.
证实了她们的后半截故事
The rest of their story checks out.
酒店经理说 向她父母收取了食物 房间和收看三集短剑风云的费用
The hotel manager says mom and dad were charged for food and a room,three pay-per-view episodes of  stiletto.
你想找死么?
Are you trying to kill yourself?
这和她们吃的是同一批食物
It's from the same batch the girls ate.
她们吃的和他一样 另外上百个健康人吃的也一样
They ate what he ate.And what a hundred other healthy people ate.
开动 中饭由Adams酒店提供
Dig in.Lunch is on the adams.
会不会 食物就是答案?
What if food is the answer?
不是这些食物 所有食物
Not this food.Any food.
Jordan说这些她全吃了
Jordan says she ate all of this.
她才16岁 正是注重外表 讲究身材的年龄
She's 16,all about body image,and she obviously worries about fitting in.
暴食症符合她的症状
Bulimia would account for her symptoms.
我们得做个钡餐检查贲门黏膜撕裂综合征 还得给她补充营养和转介心理治疗
We should do a barium swallow for mallory weiss tears,start her on nutritional supplements,get a psych consult.
为什么要看我的会议日程?
Why are you reading my program guide?
你又不打算出席任何演讲
It's not like you plan on attending any of the presentations.
我想知道我错过了多少闷蛋会议
I like to know how much boredom I'm missing.
"对化疗并发症病人的临终关怀"
"patient perceptions of complications in end-stage chemotherapy.
- 你没告诉我你要发表演讲 - 我这么做错了?
- you didn't tell me you were giving a paper. - And that was wrong?
你上次演讲时提前让我看稿子 还问我有何意见
Last time you presented a paper,you gave me an advance copy and asked for feedback.
你还好意思问 我为何不重蹈这一覆辙?
And you're wondering why I wouldn't want to repeat that experience?
噢 你看! 80年代舞会
Oh,look! An '80s party.
当你以为海鸥乐队 在你的倒后镜中渐渐远去
Just when you think  you left flock of seagulls behind in your rearview mirror,
他们却像便车客一样 突然从你眼前杀出
suddenly it's up ahead like an undead hitchhiker.
Cuddy会去
Cuddy's going.
你带了我的裤袜么?
Did you pack my leg warmers?
如果你想要她...约她出去
If you want her... ask her out.
天哪!
My god,man!
她又不是酒吧里的妓女
She's not some floozy in a bar.
而是我给我发工钱的妓女
She's the floozy I work for.
所以不能循规蹈矩地来 而是要出其不意
There's gotta be no radical steps here.Gotta be subtle.
我们恰巧在派对上偶遇
We happened to attend the same party.
又恰巧有了一番很感性的对话
The chat happens to turn personal.
像青蛙在一锅渐渐烧开的水里?
Like the frog in gradually boiling water.
没错 没等她发现怎么回事 已经被煮透端上桌了
Exactly.She'll be red and delicious before she knows it.
什么?
What?
这计划真是万无一失啊
What could possibly go wrong?
Chase这星期去了五次健身
Chase went to the gym five times this week.
是么
Okay.
其中一次我跟踪他了
One of those times I followed him.
什么?
What?
我跟踪他了 是的 我知道向你承认有多难堪
I followed him.And yes,I know how humiliating that admission is.
他去哪儿了?
Where'd he go?
- 那次确是健身中心 但我知道-- - 就此打住
- The gym,that time.But I know that something's--  I'm stopping you right there.
这番话你应该和Chase说 而不是我
This is a conversation you should be having with chase,not me.
我试过和Chase说了
I've tried having this conversation with chase.
没有撕裂 不是暴食症
No sign of tears.It's not bulimia.
他是不是有外遇了?
Is he having an affair?
不
No.
- 我为什么要相信你 - 你不必
- Why should I believe you? - You shouldn't.
你只要相信他
You should believe him.
宝贝...甜心...你还好吗?
Baby... sweetie... how are you?
- Jordan! - 窦性心律正常
- Jordan! - Normal sinus rhythm.
心跳正常
Heart rate's fine.
血压下降
Bp's dropping.
- 出什么事了? - 没有脉搏
- What's happening to her? - No pulse.
噢 上帝!
Oh,my god!
你刚不是说她心跳正常吗?
You said her heart rate was fine.
心包填塞 得马上抽出积液
Cardiac tamponade.Drain the fluid now.
怎么回事?
What is going on?
她心脏周围出血
She's bleeding around her heart.
积血抑制了她的心肌
Blood constricted her heart muscle.
我们在给她用抗心律失常药物 但不知能维持多久
She's on antiarrhythmics,but we don't know how long we can keep her stable.
看来是压力导致 当时她的父母刚--
Seemed to be triggered by stress.Her parents had just--
做钡餐检查时 她的血压下降了么?
did her blood pressure drop during the barium swallow?
- 收缩压三分钟内降到了50 - 排除慢性病的可能
- Dropped to 50 systolic in three minutes. - Rules out chronic conditions.
急性发作只能是中毒 感染
Acute conditions limit us to toxins,infections.
发病原因太多了 煤气泄漏 墙纸里的砷 花洒里的真菌
Could be anything.A gas leak,arsenic in the wallpaper,fungus in the shower.
我去她的房间和酒店取样本
I'll get samples from her room and the restaurant.
去找我们的追星女孩谈谈
Talk to our little gossip girl.
我们要明确知道过去24小时 她去过哪里 做过什么
You need to know exactly where she's been and what she's done in the last 24 hours.
噢 我想--@#$%^
Oh,I think--
欢迎出席会议 Perlmutter医生
welcome to the convention,dr.Perlmutter.
这是我连续25年参加了
It's my 25th consecutive year.
Perlmutter喜欢80年代秀
Perlmutter loves the '80s.
我不用出去吗?
Do you need me to leave too?
你可能记得她不记得的东西
You might remember stuff she doesn't.
我们把一切都告诉你了
We didn't do anything we haven't told you about.
我们在Jordan家呆了一整天
We hung out at jordan's all day.
然后我们叫了一辆加长房车进城
And then we called a limo to go into the city.
我们去了Bruce Springsteen家
We stopped at bruce springsteen's house.
Jord...不要胡闹了 好吗? 你病得很厉害
Jord... don't joke around,okay?You're really sick.
告诉他们真相
Just tell him the truth.
Bruce让我弹他第一把电吉他
Bruce let me play  the first electric guitar he ever owned.
天啊 你为什么还要说谎?
My god,why are you lying?
你为什么不相信我?
How can you not believe me?
把头转向右边
Turn to your right.
Keener先生 谢谢你肯见我
Mr.Keener,I really appreciate you coming.
噢 不费多少事 我的房间就在这儿六楼
Oh,it's not that much of a hike.My room's only six floors up.
你记得昨晚见过两个女孩吗 16岁上下?
Last night,do you remember two girls,about 16?
坐在那边的桌子
That table right there.
她们让你印象深刻呢
They made an impression.
她们老盯着你看 还笑个不停 想不注意都很难
Well,they were hard to miss with the giggling and the staring.
我想这种情况你见得多了
I'm sure that happens to you a lot.
我想你见得更多
I'm sure that happens to you a lot more.
她无法控制
She can't control it.
脑里的积血影响脑丘 使她不停地说谎
A bleed in her brain is affecting her thalamus,causing her to lie.
我们要知道一切 你们昨晚没分开过?
We need to know everything.You two were never apart?
除了她去拿冰块那会儿
Except for when she went to go get ice.
但这应该用不了多久
But that couldn't have taken very long.
- 你不记得了? - 那是在半夜里
- You don't know? - It was in the middle of the night.
她回到房间时我醒来了
I woke up when she came back into the room.
她告诉你她去拿冰块了?
And she told you she went to get ice?
*让我们随心起舞 * （By Men at Work) ("We can dance if we want to")
*we can dance if we want to *
*把你的朋友甩在身后 *
*we can leave your friends behind *
*因为你的朋友们不跳舞 如果他们不跳舞 *
*'cause your friends don't dance **and if they don't dance *
*就不是我的朋友 *
*well,they're no friends of mine *
*我们可以随心所欲 *
*say,we can act if we want to *
*如果我们不能 就没人能够 *
*if we don't,nobody will *
*你可以任意妄为... *
*and you can act real rude... *
House 是20世纪80年代
house...  1980s.
你确定?
You sure?
他们没讲清楚
They weren't specific.
你花多少钱租的这一身?
How much did it cost you to rent that?
在Wilson包里找到的
It was in wilson's bag.
Perlmutter医生 我读了你关于神经元退行性的论文
Dr. Perlmutter,I read your article on neural degeneration.
慢 你不会拿它当真吧?
Wait,you didn't really take that seriously,did you?
我只是写来捞钱的
I just wrote that for the money.
嘿 这不是珍-方达嘛
Well,hey there,jane fonda.
要不要跟我跳个舞?
Would you care to dancercize?
抱歉 我们正要进舞池
Sorry,we were just about to hit the floor.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 你的腿? - 没事儿
- Your leg? - I'm okay.
但别指望我把节奏踩准
As long as you don't expect rhythm.
记得我们上一次一起跳舞吗?
You remember the last time we danced?
医学院 我们见面的第一周
Med school,the week we met.
不
No.
我在内分泌课上见到你
I saw you in endocrinology.
跟着你去到乡村舞会
Tracked you down to the hoedown.
我是说 我们之前就见过了 在书店里
I meant,we met before that.In the bookstore.
到学校的第三天 我把课程表递给柜台后那人
My third day of school,I hand my syllabus to the guy behind the counter.
他几乎没正眼看我 只瞄了 一眼课表就说 我很有野心
He barely looks at me.Just skims the sheet and tells me I'm overly ambitious,
喜欢跟人叫板 而且喜欢去舞会
i have a chip on my shoulder,and I know how to party.
我忘记你喜欢去舞会了
I'd forgotten you knew how to party.
我说 "你胡说八道"
I said,"you're making that up.
你说 "你课表排得很满"
" and you said,"your class schedule is overloaded.
"但没一节是11点前的"
"but none of your classes are before 11:00,"
没人会选Lamb教授的课 除非他们想证明什么
and no one takes professor lamb's course unless they have something to prove.
因为Siegal教授开了一样的课 而且分数好拿得多
" because professor siegal covered the same ground and was the easier grader.
从此我盯上了你
I tracked you down.
内分泌学...还有舞会
Endocrinology... the party.
事情一件接一件发生
And one thing led to another.
最后还是不了了之
And then it didn't.
我本来想打给你
I was gonna call you.
不...不要说了
No...don't do that.
- 我没指望你有什么表示 只是... - 我本来想去找你
- There was no expectations.I was just as into it-- I was gonna come see you.
看看我们之间会发生什么
Figure out where things would go from there.
但那天早上我接到了院长电话 我被第一所医学院开除了
That was the morning I got the call from the dean and I was expelled from my first med school,
所以我想 这么做也没意义了
and there didn't seem any point.
我得回房准备明天 传染病讲座的文件
I should go to my room and review papers for the infectious disease panel.
*我的照片开始褪色 * (Time after Time By Cyndi Lauper)
*after my picture fades *
*黑色转变为灰调 *
*and darkness has turned to gray *
*从窗子往外看去... *
*watching through windows... *
喂?
Hello?
是的 谢谢告知
Yeah.Thanks for telling me.
清早七点 最好有人挂掉了
7:00 in the morning.Somebody better be dead.
我的病人 Joseph Schultz
My patient,joseph schultz.
照他的病情 这是解脱 对吧?
Under the circumstances,that's the best thing that could have happened,right?
是的 我只是希望能陪着他
Yeah.  I just wish I had been there.
昨晚没听到你回房
Didn't hear you come in last night.
是的 那时快...9:30了
Yes,and it was almost 9:30.
事情没能如你所愿?
things didn't go as you planned?
我们的关系上了一个新台阶
We've moved on to a new phase.
我告诉Cuddy我一直对她有意思 她听完就径直离开了
I tell cuddy that I've always been interested in her,and she walks out of the room.
要么是她还没准备好面对 要么就是惊讶得不知该如何反应
Well,either she just wasn't ready for that,or maybe she was just surprised and didn't know how to react.
- 你在干什么? - 你刚才表现出一丝有趣的罪恶感
- What are you doing? - Interesting reflex of guilt just now.
六周来 你的病人一直都奄奄一息
Your patient's been dying for six weeks.
你没法确定他这周末是否会死
You couldn't have predicted he'd go this weekend.
你能吗?
Or could you?
"安乐死: 说实话
"euthanasia: let's tell the truth.
我们都这么做过"
We all do it.
开场白不错
" that's a great opening line.
你疯了吗?
Are you insane?
我之前不需要你的评论 现在也不需要
I didn't want your notes before,and I don't want 'em now.
她不是去取冰块
Well,she didn't  get ice.
她去大厅了 可能去了任何地方
She got out in the lobby.She could have gone anywhere.
先看看她走了多久吧
Let's start with for how long.
快进
Fast forward.
停 倒带 倒带
Stop.Rewind.Back.
不管去了哪 也就去了大概五分钟
Wherever she went,she was only gone for,like,five minutes.
- 她手上拿着什么 - 那是Keener的日记
- She's holding something. - It's keener's journal.
他那晚肯定落在餐馆里了
He must have left it in the restaurant that night.
她折了回去 声称是她的
She went back,claimed it belonged to her.
她在找一个敲门的理由
She was looking for an excuse to knock on his door.
我知道你要说什么
I know what you're gonna say.
我没疯
I'm not insane.
医生很少受到指控
Doctors are rarely indicted.
我只是在关心你的事业
I was just thinking of your career.
但如果你是那些偶尔被控诉的医生之一 你的事业会受影响的
But yeah,if you're one of the doctors occasionally  indicted,I guess it could affect that.
总得有人揭示出 那些临死之人的生活状况
Someone needs to say what life is really like now for people who are dying.
医生会面对什么 我们要做怎样的决定
What doctors have to go through,the decisions we have to make.
没有指导 独自做出决定
Alone.Without guidance.
应该讲述出来... 写在寄给时代周刊的匿名信上
Someone should say that... in an unsigned letter to the  times.
我说的将是事实 我说的将是我们共同的想法
I'd be telling the truth.I'd be saying what we're all thinking.
谁在乎呢? 肿瘤科接受药厂的资助
Who cares?The oncology department is subsidized by drug companies.
他们不会让一个杀人犯来掌管的
They don't want it run by a murderer.
- 我们都是杀人犯 只是没胆承认而已 - 还是这句话 谁在乎呢?
- We're all murderers.We just don't have the guts to admit--  and once again,who cares?
哪里都不会雇你的
You won't be hirable anywhere.
如果说我从你身上学到了点什么
If there's one thing I've learned from you,
那就是我该坚持自己认为对的事 不计后果
it's that I should do what I think is right and not worry about the consequences.
嗯 我受用得紧
Yeah,it's worked out great for me.
无意冒犯 但我在等一个洛杉矶的电话 有话快说好吗?
Um,I don't mean  to be rude,but I'm expecting a notes call from l.A.Can we make this quick?
Jordan那晚有没有来过你房间?
Did jordan come to your room the other night?
让我换种说法吧 我们知道Jordan那晚来过你的房间
Let me put it another way.We know jordan came to your room the other night.
我很想帮忙
Look,I've tried to be helpful.
我不知道你为什么要假装我在说谎
I don't know why you want to pretend   I'm lying to you.
- 但感觉可不太好 - 我们需要搜查你的房间
- But this is getting too weird for me. - We need to search your room.
- 用不着 因为她没来过 - Allison 冷静点
- You don't,because she was never here. - Allison,calm down.
你想明哲保身? 以他人的生命为代价?
You would cover your ass at the expense of someone's life?
我们知道她给你送来了日记
We know she brought up your journal.
真是帮了大忙
That was helpful.
要是为了和未成年人的一夜情 而拿婚姻冒险 那他肯定是疯了
He'd be crazy to risk his marriage for a one-night stand with a teenager.
理智的人只会因更重要的事 来拿婚姻冒险吗?
Sensible people only risk their marriage for something more serious?
我没搞婚外情
I'm not having an affair.
- 我们在说Keener - 好的很
- We're talking about keener. - Fine.
他不在乎自己的婚姻 那事业呢? 强奸罪会毁了他的事业
He doesn't care about his marriage.What about his career?Statutory rape would ruin it.
承认强奸罪才会毁掉他的事业
It's admitting statutory rape that could ruin it.
所以我们别指望他说真话
Which is why we'll never hear the truth out of him.
过量服用迷奸药能解释她的症状 我们该用氟马西尼给她治疗
Rufies od explains all her symptoms.We should start treating her with flumazenil.
没去研讨金黃色葡萄球菌?
Isn't the mrsa panel going on?
我们被赶出来了 她开始哭了
We got kicked out.She started crying.
对 要是讨论导尿问题我也会哭
Yeah,well,discussions of urinary catheterization  will do that to me too.
保姆有点急事
The babysitter had an emergency.
哦... 你喜欢那个80年代舞会吗?
Oh...how did you like '80s night?
House告诉你了?
House talked with you?
我有种微妙的感觉
I was being subtle about it.
你突然就离开了
You left suddenly.
- 我知道House有时会很过分... - 不 他很好
- I know house can be  a little much sometimes... - no,he was sweet.
我只是学乖了 知道不能依赖他
I just know better than to rely on that.
- 他在努力了 - 对 我知道
- He's trying. - Yeah. I know.
我现在是个母亲了
I'm a mother now.
我需要一个任何时候都能依靠的人
I need a guy I can count on every single day.
那人绝不会是House
That's never been house.
不是迷奸药
It's not rufies.
她的肾脏后方在出血
She's bleeding behind her kidneys.
又输了两袋红细胞 但她还在出血
We're transfusing another two units packed red cells,but she keeps springing leaks.
看起来像是中毒反应
It looks like a toxic reaction.
Keener肯定给她吃过什么
Keener must have given her something.
他是个漫画家 不是毒贩
The guy's a comic book writer,not a drug dealer.
很多毒物都没法在标准毒筛中测出来 但他是不会告诉我们的
There's a lot that wouldn't show up in a standard tox screen.But he's never gonna tell us the truth.
她也不会告诉我们
Not gonna get the truth out of her either.
如果我们给她下药的话 她就会说
We will if we drug her.
异戊巴比妥会抑制她的丘脑活动
Amobarbital would suppress her thalamus.
她在用抗心律不齐的药 异戊巴比妥可能会导致心脏停跳
She's on antiarrhythmics.Amobarbital could stop her heart.
她已经要死了
She's already dying.
你在生我的气
You're angry at me.
你怪罪在这男人身上 是因为你觉得他也在说谎
You're taking it out on this guy 'cause you think  he's lying to you too.
你会害死病人的
And you're gonna kill our patient in the process.
- 我们得知道真相 - 我们该打电话给House
- We need to know the truth. - We should call house.
对 他会叫我们小心点
Yeah. He'll recommend we take the cautious approach.
- 要饼干吗? - 这些会记在我的信用卡上 7块一包
- Pretzel? - Those are gonna show up on my credit card at seven bucks a bag.
楼下有自助餐
There's an all-you-can-eat buffet downstairs.
研究表明 当10元的酒作价90元时 会好喝很多
Studies show that $10 wine tastes better if you're told that it costs $90.
我相信在葡萄汁上也能适用
I'm sure the same thing st be true of grape soda.
来喝点吧
Have one.
我们可以为你的事业终结而干杯
We can toast your ending unemployment.
你可以坐在这 不断刷新我的酒店账单 或者去追求你喜欢的女人
Yes,you can sit here running up my hotel bill,or you can go get the woman of your dreams.
我可不知道默克尔会参加会议 (默克尔 德国女总理)
I didn't know angela merkel was attending the conference.
我刚和Cuddy谈过 她觉得你不可靠
I just spoke with cuddy.She doesn't think you're reliable.
在她改主意之前 你们只会是朋友
And you will remain friend-zoned  until that changes.
我没法让她相信仅一个周末 我就完全改变了性格
I can't convince her  that I've changed my entire personality in a weekend.
对 但你可以采取主动
Yeah,but you could make the first step.
- 她需要什么? - 今天需要一个保姆
- What does she need? - Today,a babysitter.
- 你在想什么? - 海湾
- What are you thinking about? - Fjords.
看到没? 认真点
You see?Seriously.
我知道你会觉得不舒服 但别搞花样
I know this is out of your comfort zone,but don't scheme.
- 别... 照做就是 - 你告诉我 得让她看到我的改变
- Don't...just do the deed-- you tell me that I've gotta show her I've changed,
但你却表现得不相信我能做到
and yet you act like you don't believe I can.
- 如果我没法说服我最好的朋友... - 抱歉
- If I can't convince my best friend... -  I'm sorry.
我不是... 我不是... 我不是...
I didn't mean--  I didn't mean...  I didn't mean...
你给我下了药
you drugged me.
她还是没你比较好
She's better off without you.
这么说会伤人的
Words can hurt,you know.
我以为吐真剂只会出现在 那些差劲的间谍片里
I thought truth serum was only stuff they gave people in lame spy movies.
我们知道你很害怕 但我们也知道你想说出真话
We know you're scared.But we know you want to tell the truth.
我们会帮你的
We're gonna help you do that.
那晚去他房间之后 你和 Jeffrey Keener之间发生了什么?
What happened between you and jeffrey keener   the night you went up to his room?
我都不敢相信他和我说话了
I couldn't believe he even talked to me.
我告诉他 他的作品对我来说意味深刻
I told him how much his work means to me.
我知道自己听起来就像个白痴
I figured I must sound like a moron.
但他人很好
But he was nice about it.
他说我很特别
He said I was special.
心跳加速
Heart rate's increasing.
140 可以接受 让她说
140's acceptable.Let her talk.
他有没有给过你什么? 喝的或者是药片?
Did he give you anything?A drink,pills?
他说那是迷幻药
He said it was ecstasy.
但看着不像 也没有迷幻药的感觉
But it didn't look like ecstasy,and it didn't really make me feel how ecstasy usually does.
那你是什么感觉?
How did it make you feel?
让我感觉很累
It just made me really tired.
看起来什么样子? 胶囊还是药片?
What did it look like?A capsule?Tablet?
- 是药片 圆的 - 可能是锂
- It was a tablet.Round. - Could be lithium.
然后他开始碰我
He just started touching me.
一开始感觉还不错
At first it seemed nice.
但之后... 我不想污蔑他
But then... I didn't want to insult him.
够了
That's enough.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我很爱你们 但我... 我感觉我让你们失望了
I love you guys so much,and I just-- I feel like I've let you down.
我要杀了他 我要杀了那个混蛋
I'm gonna kill him.I'm gonna kill that son of a bitch.
先别急 看这个
Before you do that,look here.
眶骨膜处的血流量增加
Increased periorbital blood flow throughout.
说明她说的都是谎话
It means everything she's been saying has been a lie.
都是谎话?
Everything?
那你还是不知道她怎么了?
S-so you still don't know what's wrong with her?
抱歉
Sorry.
噢 我还以为是客房服务
Oh,I thought you were room service.
你的病人出问题了?
Something going on with your patient?
里面很安静 Rachel睡了?
It's quiet in there.Is rachel asleep?
我想你也许需要一个保姆
I thought maybe you could use a babysitter.
实际上 我把她送到楼下的日托中心去了
Actually,I've got her in day care downstairs.
好
Great.
下次我再帮手吧
Maybe later.
- 嗨 House - 嗨 Lucas
- Hey,house. - Hey,lucas.
- 这可真尴尬 - 有点
- This is awkward. - A bit.
我走了大概就不会尴尬了吧
That awkwardness would probably go away if I left.
我是Foreman 想告诉House病情进展 但他关机了
It's foreman.I'm trying to update house,but his phone's off.
House
House!
他不在这儿
He's not here.
病人失血比我们输血的速度还快
Patient's losing blood faster than we can transfuse.
Cameron上网搜查发现Keener带着狗旅行 --我们想按照立克次体治疗
Cameron did an online search and found out keener travels with his dog-- we're treating for rickettsia.
- 知道他现在哪儿么? - 噢！不！
- Any idea where he is? - Oh,no!
我五分钟前就该去演讲了
I was supposed to be giving a paper five minutes ago.
好...好...
Okay...okay...
Wilson大夫让我带他 向大家道歉 他来不了了
dr.Wilson has asked me to tender his apologies for his absence.
你们将听到我的文章
You'll be hearing my paper instead.
很不幸 没来得及修正会议的安排表
Unfortunately,there wasn't time to correct the program schedule.
"安乐死" 让我们把真相说出来
"euthanasia:  "let's tell the truth.
"我们都这么做 我们只是不说出口" 我们玩这种游戏
"we all do it."we just don't talk about it."we play the game.
我们用别的措辞 或者我们什么都不说
"we use other words   or we don't use any words at all.
好文法
Nice phrasing.
你好?
Hello?
呃...我不知道我想找那个部门
Uh...i don't know what department I want.
我需要...裤子
Uh,I need...pants.
病人为男性 55岁 肺癌晚期
Patient s,a 55-year-old man."end-stage lung cancer.
他的痛苦甚至超过了 我们假装可以治疗的程度
"his pain was beyond the point   "where we could even pretend to treat it.
我教他如何使用吗啡针
"i showed him how to use the morphine pump.
我告诉他过量吗啡会致命 但不用担心
"i told him too much morphine would kill him,"but not to worry.
这机器只会提供限定的量
"the machine only gives out so much.
要过量使用的话需要密码
"to override it you need to enter a special code.
我走出门 告诉护士密码是328
"i went to the door  "and told the nurse,'the code is 328.
我说得很大声
'  "i said it loudly.
当他第一次来我办公室的时候 我告诉他 每一步路我都会陪着他
"when he first came to my office,"i told him I would be with him every step of the way.
但我最后抛下了他
"but I left him alone at the end.
我因怯懦而打破了承诺 我失败了--
"i broke that promise  to cover my ass,I failed--"
这句话我写错了
i was wrong when I wrote that.
我一直都是尽我所能地付出
I've never given any less than my best.
我总是在承担责任
I am incapable of turning away from a responsibility.
我的好友经常利用这点
My friends take advantage of that fact far too often.
我知道我已经给了他 我能给予的一切
I know that I gave that man everything I could.
我知道他也明白
And I know that he knew that too.
这个负担 没人应该独自承担
"this is a burden no one should have to carry alone.
这个决定也没有人能独自定夺
And this is a decision no one should make alone.
因为坦白说 我不相信你们
"  because frankly,I don't trust all of you.
医生…?
Doctor. Doctor. Doctor? Doctor?
- 提问... - 原谅我 医生
- Question... - excuse me,doctor.
你真有勇气
Not many people would have your courage.
谢谢你 Perlmutter医生
Thank you,dr.Perlmutter.
在我大吵之前 Foreman说他们怀疑是立克次体
Before I start shouting,foreman says they're looking at rickettsia.
谢谢你转告 继续
Thanks for the message.Continue.
搞什么鬼? 你觉得一个小小的表白 就能让我忘记你对我下药
What the hell?You think that little shout-out is gonna make me forget that you drugged me
藏起我的裤子 偷我的发言稿?
,hid my pants,stole my speech?
你想让这篇文章发表 它已经发表了
You wanted the paper out there,it's out there.
而且你的工作也保住了 那是我的文章
And your job is safe.That was my paper.
你不问我想要什么 不顾我的意愿 你对我下药了
You don't ask what I want,you ignore my wishes,you drug me.
我在等你为我们关系重新命名
I'm waiting for you to name something new to our relationship.
你没理由对我生气
You've got no good reason to be angry with me.
真的吗? 我应该感谢你?
Oh,really?I should be thanking you?
如果这是为了让文章公之于众 那是的
If this was about getting the story out there,then yeah.
当然 如果这是为了别的什么...
Of course,if this is actually about something else...
可能病人奄奄一息 让你觉得无能为力 你需要做一些伟岸的 愚蠢的举动
maybe you feeling impotent because patients keep dying and you think you need to make some grand,stupid gesture-
你想当个英雄-- 那么 对不起
you need to be a hero-- well,then,yeah,sorry.
我确实搞糟了
I did screw it up.
你太过分了 这不是你的决定
You stepped over the line.This was not your decision.
我的上帝 这个国家有10,000个肿瘤学家
My god,there are 10,000 oncologists in this country.
每个人都死过病人
Every one of them loses patients.
但只有你会感觉内疚...
But only you would feel guilty enough...
当然了 连吵架也不能按照我的时间表
of course,we can't even argue on my schedule.
我是House
It's house.
把袋子取下来
Take down the bags.
- 现在判断药物是否有效还太早- - 不是药袋子
- It's too soon to tell if the meds are gonna--  it's not the meds.
要她命的是那些血
It's the blood that's killing her.
大家什么反应 你们都大吃一惊了 是吧?
What's everybody doing?You're stunned,right?
- 我是说 血? - 她有内出血
- I mean,blood? - She's had internal bleeding.
- 她需要血来? - 这是她妈妈吗?
- She needs the blood to-- is that the mom?
如果是的话 我能解释下
I've got a good comeback if it's the mom.
是的 我是她的母亲
Yes,I'm her mother.
当然 她需要血 如果你想杀死她的话
Sure,she needs blood,if you want to kill her.
你就没人可忽略的了? 好主意
Then you'd have nobody left to neglect--great plan.
你的女儿感染了致伤弧菌 美味的牡蛎的附赠品
Your daughter has vibrio vulnificus,courtesy of a few scrumptious oysters on the half shell.
我没有吃过牡蛎
I didn't eat any oysters.
这就证明了她吃了 伙计们 这真棒
Thus proving that she did.Boy,that's neat.
100个人都吃了那些牡蛎
100 other people ate those oysters.
- 我也吃了 - 是她爸爸吗?
- I ate-- is that the dad?
- 我能解释 - 是Chase
- I've got a good comeback-- it's chase.
我还想她爸爸可能也是个澳洲人
Oh,I thought the dad might've been australian too.
牡蛎没问题 牡蛎都有弧菌
There was nothing wrong with the oysters.All oysters have vibrio.
但是几乎没人有血色沉着病
But almost no one has hemochromatosis.
血色沉着病让弧菌易感 导致了肿胀
It'd give here a unique susceptibility to vibrio,cause the swollen joints.
但却被误归于暴食症 所以给她用营养剂
But it got attributed to bulimia,so she got supplements.
- 那含铁 - 铁把肝脏烧坏了 导致了出血
- With iron. - Which overcooked the liver,which caused bleeding.
输血 加铁 流血 输血
More blood,more iron,more bleeding,more blood.
她会好起来吗?
Is she going to be okay?
除非给她用高剂量的头孢他啶治疗弧菌 螯合治疗血色沉着
Only if we give her high-dose ceftazidime  for the vibrio and chelate for the hemochromatosis.
现在 Cameron 拿起电话 给我来个戏剧性的退场
Now,cameron,pick up the phone and give me a dramatic exit.
那么...你们两个疯孩子是怎么勾搭上的?
So...how'd you two crazy kids hook up?
我怀疑会计部有人偷钱 我想私下调查
I suspected someone in accounting was skimming money,and I wanted to investigate quietly.
我唯一认识的私家侦探是你介绍的
And since you introduced me to the only detective I know...
事情一件接一件发生
and one thing leads to another.
为什么保密?
Why keep it a secret?
你是在我脆弱的时候保护我么?
You protecting me in my fragile state?
你觉得我是个疯子 如果听到坏消息的时机不对 就会错乱?
You think I was an unhinged looney  who was about to go off the rails at a badly timed bit of news?
我只是不想私生活太招摇
I just don't advertise my personal life.
我需要有人帮助照顾宝宝 Lucas赶来了
I needed help with the baby.Lucas drove up.
是的 她很担心 是有一点担心
Yeah. She was worried. A little worried.
像朋友那样
As a friend.
我必须躲在房间里 见不得光
I had to hide in our room and be the dirty little secret.
有点不爽
Kinda sucked.
我告诉她这没有必要 你有想跟她上床的幻想
I told her it wasn't necessary.So you had some hallucination  about having sex with her.
- 我觉得我们没有必要谈论- - 我意思是 我总是想象和女人上床
- I don't think we need to talk-- I mean,I imagine having sex with women all the time.
没什么大不了的
No big deal.
当然要是她们知道我想象的内容 会很尴尬
Though I guess if they knew what I imagine,it could get awkward.
我猜这有点不同 因为在你的幻想中 她是你的救赎者
And I guess it's different because in the fantasy,she was your savior.
但 那也是几个月前的事了 对吗?
But I mean,that was months ago,right?
好不容易你才能恢复理智 -进了精神病院
All the work that you had to do to get straight-- you've been institutionalized.
你有更重要的事情要做 我该闭嘴了
You've had way bigger stuff to deal with.I should shut up.
你要一杯姜汁汽水吗?
Can I buy you a ginger ale?
姜汁汽水不错 要加柠檬
A ginger ale would be good.With lemon.
感染清除干净了 你几天后就能出院了
Infection's clearing up nicely.You should be out of here in a few days.
那太好了
Oh,that is wonderful.
Jack 你好吗?
Jack,how are you?
亲爱的 你爸爸和我觉得我们应该放个假
Sweetie,your father and I think  we should reward ourselves with a little time off.
那个会议得等上几周
That meeting's gonna have to wait a couple of weeks.
我们还不能走
We're staying here.
你想去什么地方
You should think about where you'd like to go.
亲爱的 他们说奠基的设计图纸错了
Honey,they're saying the specs are wrong for the whole foundation.
你能跟他们说说吗?
Can you at least come talk to 'em?
给我吧
Let me see.
- 你还好吗? - 是的
- You okay? - Yeah.
不 地基土工程报告没问题
No.Soil engineering report was fine.
- 我习惯了 - 你在跟谁说话?
- I'm used to it. - Who are you talking to?
那...那晚究竟发生了什么
So...about what happened that night.
我甚至没勇气敲门
I never even got up the courage to knock on his door.
那好 你把他们的号码发给我
Well,you'll have to send me their numbers.
耶!
Yea!
那是什么?
What is that?
你要开车吗?
Are you driving?
他看起来像个能始终依靠的人
He looks like a guy who'd be there every day.
小冰箱又装满了
Minibar is restocked.
- 我们拿些小饼干路上吃吧- - 当你也像我那么做时
- I say we grab some pretzels for the road-- when you do what I did,
光是告诉自己你没做错是不够的
it's not enough to tell yourself you did nothing wrong.
你必须从别人嘴里听到
You need to hear it from someone else.
如果没得到上帝或者社会的原谅 那就得有朋友支持
If not god or society,a friend.
否则你会疯的
Otherwise you go crazy.
你当时对我说的话...谢谢
What you said to me up there... thank you.
你是个好朋友
You're a good friend.
Cuddy应该意识到
Cuddy should know that.
是 你该让她知道我对你下药 阻止你承认谋杀
Yeah,you should let her know that I drugged you so you wouldn't confess to murder.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
万一有人认出你呢
Someone could have recognized you.
15年来我第一次参加全美医生联会
First u.S. Conference I've attended in 15 years.
Perlmutter呢?
Perlmutter?
整个周末在多伦多充分的不在场证明
Toronto,all weekend.Airtight alibi.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不知道 为什么我总是朝最坏的地方想
I don't know why I always suspect the worst.
如果你说你没有外遇 我相信你
If you say you're not having an affair,you're not having an affair.
天哪 你有
Oh,god,you are.
- 我没有 - 好的 对不起 再一次
- I'm not. - Okay. Sorry.Again.
如果你不想说…也行
If you don't want to tell...okay.
但我可以帮你
But I could help.
无论这是什么事 它在折磨你
Whatever this is,it's eating away at you.
我们能一起渡过
We could get past it together.
无论怎样我都爱你
I love you no matter what.
我们有时会救不了病人
We lose patients sometimes.
有一个病人...Dibala...
One of those patients... dibala...
事实上不是--并不是我们救不了他
we didn't ac-- we didn't actually lose him.
我杀了他
I killed him.